어지러운 전국 시대.
It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over
Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
Karakuri Martial Artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri Martial Artist!
무사시 등장이오!
Musashi is here-dasu!
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden
Musashi Road
(The Story of Karakuri Martial Artist: Road of Musashi)
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
A man always dreams of the day
제일 강해질 날을
in the center of the world to become
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
AH! AH! the strongest
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
모험의 길의 막을 연다
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes a life dazzle
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
내일은 빛난다
Tomorrow will be glorious
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes a life dazzle
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Fight the utmost with the stillness
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
His eyes shined! Musashi!!
도망치던 무사시는 쥬베와의 번외 시합을 벌이게 되었지만
Musashi once was running away, but he managed to have an extra match against Jube.
야규신카게류의 비검 앞에 완전히 패배의 쓴맛을 보았다.
But he ended in defeat in front of the secret sword of Yagyu Shinkage Style.
의기소침해 바깥으로 나온 무사시를 기다리고 있던 것은 한조의 무서운 함정이었다.
Dispirited, Musashi went out, and Hanzo's frightening trap was waiting for him.
카라쿠리 검호 총출격
Go Out at Once!
Karakuri Martial Artists
이제 대회는 준결승, 코지로와 우시와카의 대결입니다!
Kojirō vs. Ushiwaka's match begins soon!
어디보다도 빠른 우리 회사 신보 삽쇼, 삽쇼!
Our newspaper is faster than anybody else! Buy 'em!
꽤나 재빠른 놈이군.
He's pretty fast.
뭐하나, 코지로! 옴싹달싹하질 못하나!
What's wrong, Kojirō? Can't you handle him at all?
우시와카의 분신술 앞에서 그 대단한 코지로도 손발을 꼼짝이질 못한다.
In front of Ushiwaka's technology, even the famous Kojirō couldn't handle him.
넷이나 보였지만, 이대로 포기할 코지로가 아니었다.
He saw four Ushiwakas, but Kojirō isn't a person who'd give up by this.
보였다!
Got him!
거기까지!
Stop!
승부 났소!
Match set!
코지로, 대단하구먼.
Kojirō's pretty good.
그 동안, 한조의 저택에 잡힌 무사시는...
Meanwhile, Musashi trapped in Hanzo's mansion was...
아무나!
Anyone!
아무나 있소?!
Is there anyone-dasu?!
들리긴 하오?!
Can you hear me-dasu?
할 말이 있소!
I have something to say-dasu!
시끄럽다, 이 애새끼가!
Shut up, you brat!
닥치지 않으면 썰어버린다!
If you don't shut up, I'll chop you up!
베려면 베어 보시오!
Chop me up if you can-dasu!
뭐래, 이 새끼가!
So what, you bastard!
날 속이고 멋대로 사형을 정하다니 절대 용서할 수 없소!
Deceive me and arrange execution as you please? Completely unforgivable-dasu!
한조 님이 정했다. 버둥쳐도 소용없다!
It's Lord Hanzo's decision. A struggle is futile!
난 나쁜 짓 따위 하지 않았소!
I never did something bad-dasu!
제니가탄 두목도 알고 있소!
Even Boss Zenigatan knows that!
관계 없어, 그런 거.
That has nothing to do with this.
그런 게 어디 있소! 난 절대 사형받을 수는 없소!
That's nonsense-dasu! I cannot be executed-dasu!
멋대로 지껄여라!
Yeah, right!
나 여기서 나가겠소!
I'm getting out of here-dasu!
결승전을 보고 싶소!
I want to see the final match-dasu!
작작 좀 해라!
That's enough!
혹시나 했지만 제 감이 틀렸던 모양이니...
I hoped something, but I guess I was wrong.
그래, 시합에도 나가지 못한 무사시가 조용히 구경에 올 리가 없지.
Right. Musashi wouldn't just go see when he couldn't even join the match.
그렇네요.
That's right.
그렇게 힘이 넘쳤으니까...
He was so vigorous...
그래도 하찮은 짓을 해서 무예 대회를 헛것으로 만들었군, 무사시 놈.
But still, Musashi really made all his way to the competition to a total waste.
무사시 씨, 대체 어디로 가 버린 거에요?
Mr. Musashi, where did you disappear to?
지금부터 어쩔 셈이죠?
What are you going to do from now on?
뭘! 이렇게 된 바 내가 뭐가 어떻게 되더라도 찾아 줄 테니까!
Don't worry! As things like this happened, I'll find him no matter what!
이 이상 소란을 피우지 않으면 됐지.
It's already good enough that he's not making a fuss.
자, 자, 기다리고 기다리셨던 결승전이 시작됩니다!
The final match that you waited and waited will begin soon!
당사 예상대로 야규 쥬베와 미검사 코지로의 한판승부.
As we expected, it will be one-time match of Yagyu Jube versus Kojirō, the beautiful swordsman.
우승은 누구일까! 예상은 적중률 제일의 당사가 지팡구 제일이요!
Who will win? Our company has the highest accuracy in Jipangu!
네, 여기요, 여기요!
Yes, here, here!
쥬베 님보다도 역시!
Better than Mr. Jube...
코지 님이지!
is Koji!
-코지 님 정말 멋져!
-보여줘, 보여줘!
-Mr. Koji is so cool!
-Let me see!
이 눈이 좋아!
I like these eyes!
꼭 코지 님이 이겼으면 좋겠어!
I wish Mr. Koji win in the match!
쥬베 대 코지로인가...
Jube vs. Kojirō?
누구든 무사시였으면 좋았을 텐데...
If one of them was Musashi, it could have been better.
나도 코지로 씨는 알고 있어요.
I know Mr. Kojirō too.
분명, 승부를 내고 싶었겠지요, 무사시 씨.
Mr. Musashi, you probably wanted to settle this with him.
그럼 지금부터 지팡구 무예대회 결승전을 개시합니다!
We'll soon begin the final match of Jipangu Martial Arts Competition!
야규 쥬베 님!
Mr. Yagyu Jube!
한쪽은 미스터 코지로 님!
Mister Kojirō on this side!
승부는 단판 승부.
It is an one-game match.
코지로 님, 어리지만 대단한 무예를 mochiusida.
Mr. Kojirō. A young grown man with splendid martial arts skills.
쥬베 님, 처음 부족함이 없는 무예가하고 만났다.
Mr. Jube. It is the first time facing a martial artist without a flaw.
잡았다!
Chance!
이야... 대단하군.
Yes, that's awesome!
이야! 대단해, 코지 님!
So cool, Mr. Koji!
부탁이니 꼭 이겨요!
Please! Get the victory!
내 타를 피할 줄이야.
He evaded my hit.
지금 이것으로는 역시 쥬베 님이라고 말하기에 부족함이 없다.
That is Mr. Jube I know. This is the only thing that I can say by this.
확실히 기술도 자질도 비범한 사내.
He is a man with extraordinary technique and talent.
그러나, 젊음을 과신하는 것이 보인다.
But I can see him placing too much confidence in his youthfulness.
그 쯤 무사시는...
Meanwhile, Musashi was...
젠장! 이렇게 될 거라면 굽든 꼬치를 만들어 먹든 마음대로!
Damn! Do whatever you want, burn me, or make a skew out of me-dasu!
그러면 곤란하오. 죽으면 모든 건 펑.
No, I can't let that happen-dasu. If I die, everything is pop!
뭐가 어떻게 되라도 여기서 나가 보이겠소!
No matter what, I will get out of this place!
결승전은 시작되고, 금세 한순간에 끝이 나려 하고 있었다.
The final match had begun, and it was about to end right away.
츠바메가에시.
Tsubamegaeshi.
흥미롭구나.
Interesting.
잡았다!
Chance!
야규신카게류 비검.
Secret Sword of Yagyu Shinkage Style.
등롱 흘리기!
Tourou Nagashi!
승부 났소이다! 쥬베 님의 승리!
Match set! Mr. Jube wins!
그래, 훌륭하다. 정말 드물게 질 높은 시합이었다.
Right, good job. A rare match of truly high quality.
나는 만족이군.
I am satisfied.
내가... 졌다...
I... lost...
이 내가 진 것이다...
I, here, lost, now...
어째서인가...
How come...
내 어디에 과실이...
Where did I make mistake?
코지로 님.
Mr. Kojirō.
시합에서 이겼지만, 비등했습니다.
While I won the match, it was an even match.
훌륭한 칼솜씨, 감복했습니다.
I admire your excellent swordsmanship.
쥬베 님이야말로.
Same for me too.
코지 님이 졌어! 이런 건 싫어!
Mr. Koji lost! I hate this!
나 슬퍼... 죽고 싶어!
I'm so sad... I wanna die!
쥬베 님의 우승인가... 훌륭하군.
So Mr. Jube wins... Excellent.
역시 대단하오.
You are superb.
쥬베 놈, 이걸로 점점 이에야스의 신망을 모아 쇼군의 힘을 얻겠다는 것 같다만,
It seems that that damned Jube is trying to gain confidence from Ieyasu and gain the power of Shogun...
곧 울상을 지을 때가 꼭 온다.
The time for you to make a tearful face will come.
그것을 위해서도 내 비밀을 아는 그 방해자를 소멸해야만 한다.
Also for that, I must exterminate that obstacle who knows my secret.
지금부터 제 1회 지팡구 무예 대회 우승자의 시상식을 실시합니다!
From now on, we will begin the award ceremony of the 1st Jipangu Martial Arts Competition!
그 쯤, 한조의 저택에서는...
Meanwhile, in Hanzo's mansion...
놓아! 어쩔 생각이냐! 이놈!
Let me go! What are you going to do with me-dasu? Hey!
무사시의 처형히 집행되려 하고 있다. 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Musashi's execution is about to start. Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
야규신카게류, 쥬베 님!
Yagyu Shinkage Style, Mr. Jube!
우승. 야규신카게류 야규 쥬베.
Champion. Yagyu Jube of Yagyu Shinkage Style.
귀공은 제 1회 지팡구 무예 대회에서 빼어난 기술을 모두에게 보여주었소.
You showed your excellent techniques in the 1st Jipangu Martial Art Competition to everyone.
우수하게 우승한 것을 인정하여 여기 상장 및 상금 천 량을 드리오이다.
We award you the certificate of championship and prize one thousand ryos.
천, 천 량일고?
Tho- thousand ryos?
대단해!
Awesome!
젠장!
Damn!
형이 우승했어야 했는데.
Our brother should have won...
뭐야, 저 사람?
Who's that guy?
아빠, 큰일이야!
Dad, I got a big problem!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
잠깐 비켜봐!
Move for a moment!
센히메, 지금 수상식의...
Senhime, we're in the middle of...
안됐지만 그럴 때가 아니야! 무사시 씨가 한조에게 잡혀서 저택에 끌려갔어!
I'm sorry, but this is no time for that! Hanzo captured Mr. Musashi and took him to his mansion!
무사시?
Musashi?
오, 쥬베하고 번외 시합을 했던 그 남자?
Oh, that man who had an extra match against Jube?
부탁이야, 빨리 구해 줘.
Please, rescue him right now.
구한다니?
Rescue him?
할아버진 쇼군이잖아! 뭐라도 할 수 있는 거 아니야?
Aren't you a Shogun, grandpa? Aren't you supposed to be able to do anything?
진정해라, 센히메. 그 남자는 반역을 저질러서!
Calm down, Senhime. That man has done a treachery!
그러니까 그게 아니야. 그냥 무예 대회에 늦었을 뿐이야!
That's not it! He was just late for the competition.
그래도 내가 아무리 쇼군이라고 해도 반역자로 지명수배됐던 남자를...
But still, even for a Shogun, it's difficult to pardon someone who was wanted as a traitor...
뭔 소리야? 늦으면 무고한 사람이 사형돼!
What are you talking about? If we're late, a innocent people will be executed!
그, 그래도 말야...
B- but still...
쇼군!
Shogun!
쥬베, 부탁드릴 것이 있습니다.
I, Jube, has a request.
뭔가, 쥬베?
What is it, Jube?
실례입니다만, 이번 보상금은 받지 않겠습니다.
Excuse me, but I will not receive the award.
음? 무슨 소리인가?
What do you mean?
그 대신, 무사시 님의 구출을 저도 부탁드립니다.
Instead, I also ask you to order rescuing Musashi.
뭐라, 상 대신 무사시를 돕겠다?
So, you'd like to help Musashi instead of receiving award?
무사시 님은 훌륭한 무예가.
Mr. Musashi is a fine Martial Artist.
이대로 딱 한 분을 구해 주시기를 바라오니 부탁드립니다.
Like this, I want to ask you to save one person.
쥬베 씨!
Mr. Jube!
소생도 부탁드리오이다!
I request for that too!
꼭 무사시 님을 구해 주십시오.
Please, rescue Mr. Musashi by all means.
무사시는 장래 있는 젊은이요! 구해 주시라!
Musashi is a young man with a bright future! Rescue him!
그런 사내라도 무예가 축에는 낍니다. 구해 주기를 부탁드립니다.
Even that kind of man qualifies as a Martial Artist. Please save him.
이 정도의 부탁이 있다면 알겠다. 들어 주겠어.
With the request from this many people, alright, I'll do.
-할아버지, 고마워!
-딸의 부탁이라면.
-Thank you, grandpa!
-Hey, hey!
끝이겠구나, 무사시.
It's the end, Musashi.
뭐, 뭣이오, 방금은.
Wh- what was that for-dasu?
이하닌자술 작렬! 다음은 너다!
Bursting Iga Ninja Technique! Next is you!
결국 나도...
Finally, me too...
오츠루 씨...
Otsuru...
나, 지팡구 제일이 되지 못하고... 분하오...
I go before becoming the number one in Jipangu... I'm so frustrated-dasu...
안 돼요. 절대 죽으면 안 돼요! 지팡구 제일이 되세요, 무사시 씨!
No. You must not die. Become the number one in Jipangu, Mr. Musashi!
오츠루 씨...
Otsuru...
처형대 준비!
Prepare to execute!
-반역자!
-멋대로 하는 건 용서하지 못한다!
-You traitor!
-You're not doing as you want!
뭔 일이냐!
What's going on?
코지로! 우시와카! 모두!
Kojirō! Ushiwaka! Everyone!
무례하다. 무슨 짓인가!
How rude! What are you doing?
쥬베 님.
Mr. Jube.
쥬베 씨?
Mr. Jube?
일단 이곳은 쇼군의 직속 밀정, 이가 닌자 한조의 저택이다.
First, this place is the mansion of Iga Ninja Hanzo, the Shogun's spy.
설마 쥬베 님이라 하더라도 반역은 용서할 수 없다.
Even for you, Mr. Jube, I will not forgive your treachery.
처형은 취소되었다.
The execution has been canceled.
무사시 님의 사슬을 풀어 드려라.
Untie the chain on Mr. Musashi.
뭐시라? 녀석은 쇼군을 거슬러 반역을 저지른 천하의 반역자!
What? That bastard is the incomparable traitor who defied Shogun!
뭐에 눈이 뒤집혀 계시나?
Why did you lose your mind?
명령이다!
It's an order!
이에야스 님의 증명서다!
A warrant from Mr. Ieyasu!
무, 무슨. 뭔가 착각이...
Th- there... there must be a mistake...
닥쳐라! 쇼군 직필 증명서를 의심하는가!
Shut up! Are you questioning the ceritifcate directly written by Shogun?
그 쪽이야말로 반역자가 될 터이다!
You will become the traitor instead!
건방지다! 숙여라!
How impudent! Lower your head!
예, 예!
Ye- yessir!
이제 걱정할 건 없어.
There's nothing to worry about anymore.
-바이켄!
-정말 다행이구나!
-Baiken!
-What a relief!
-코지로!
-그만해라! 창피하다!
-Kojirō!
-Stop that! That's embarrassing!
위태로웠다. 시간을 겨우 맞춘 게 다행이었다.
It was a risky moment. It's a relief that we could make it in the right time.
쥬베 씨! 무사시... 무사시, 이대로이오!
Mr. Jube! Musashi... Musashi thanks you as you see!
나, 행복하오.
I am so happy-dasu.
이런 기쁜 일은 지금껏 없었소!
There never was something as happy as this-dasu!
무예가라는 자가, 사람들 보는 앞에서 목놓고 우는 놈이 있나, 무사시!
Is there a Martial Artist who cries loudly in front of people, Musashi?!
눈물이 아니오! 눈의 땀이오!
This is not a tear-dasu! It's a sweat of eyes-dasu!
눈의 땀이오...
Sweat of eyes...
검사들의 뜨거운 우정에 구해져
Rescued by the burning friendship of swordsmen,
눈이 땀이 멈추질 않소...
Sweat of eyes isn't stopping-dasu...
지금은 더 이상 고집도 체면도 없이 단지 행복한 눈물을 흘릴 뿐인 무사시였다.
Musashi was simply crying happily, without stubbornness nor honor.
다행이구나.
What a relief.
네이놈, 쥬베 놈.
Jube, you bastard...
이렇게 된 바에는 이 한조가 무사시를 반드시 지옥으로 보내 주겠다.
Since it came to this, I, Hanzo, will send Musashi to hell no matter what.
이렇게 찾아도 발견하지 못하다니, 정말 어디에 갔을까요...
Even after looking for him so hardly we couldn't find him. Where could he go to?
무예 대회에도 나오지 않고...
He wasn't in the competition too...
무예 대회는 내년도 있다.
There is a competition next year too.
다음 1년도 열심히 수련하면 되겠구나.
It'll be all right if he train strictly for another year.
스님! 오츠루 씨!
Monk! Ms. Otsuru!
두목, 그렇게 황급히...
Boss, you're rushing!
이게 황급하게 알릴 일 아니면 뭐요!
This is something I must rush to tell you!
알아냈어요!
I found him!
무사시 씨 어디 있는지 알아냈어!
I found where Musashi is!
정말로?
Really?
어, 어디에?
Wh- where?
걸어가면서 이야기하지.
I'll tell you during walking.
자! 서둘러!
Hurry up!
오츠루 씨...
Otsuru!
제니가탄 두목이... 여러 큰 일이 있었네요.
Boss Zenigatan told me... I see you have gone through many things.
사랑이라 불러보지도 못하고
We did not called it a love yet
응. 아, 저...
Yeah, that is...
한결같은 것도 좋지만, 이 무슨 너무한 일이니.
Being consistent is good, but that was too much.
이별이 왔어요
and it's already time to separate
쌓인 이야기도 있고 하니 집에 돌아가서 천천히!
There are a lot to talk about, so let's go back to the home and slowly do it!
제니가탄 두목.
Boss Zenigatan.
무사시 님은 이제 성으로 가야만 한다.
Mr. Musashi must go to the castle now.
아무렇지 않던 어제가
Casual yesterday has become
그런 관계로...
So...
괜찮아요. 무사시 씨의 건강한 얼굴을 보니 안심되네요.
It's alright. Seeing the healthy face of Musashi makes me relieved.
둘의 추억
the memory between us
이걸로 마음을 다잡고 마을로 돌아가자꾸나, 오츠루.
As we found out Musashi is all right, let's calm down and go back, Otsuru.
석양을 바라보는 당신의 옆모습
Your profile of looking at the sunset
내년은 힘내요. 꼭.
You'll get what you want next year, no matter what.
물론이오!
Of course-dasu!
사랑을 숨긴 띠가 가슴을 조여온답니다
The belt that covered the love is tightening my heart
나, 건강하게 해내겠소!
I'll do it safely and perfectly-dasu!
마을의 모두에게 전해주오!
Say hi to people in the village!
오츠루 씨... 나, 꼭...
Otsuru... I will do it...
울지는 않아요
I won't cry or something
걱정하지 마세요
so don't worry
당신만큼이나
As much as you do
밝게 살고 있어요
I'm living brightly
이, 이 내가 쇼군 님의 손녀님의 경호 역할?
I... I'll guard the granddaughter of Shogun?
인 것이오?
Is that right-dasu?
그렇다. 신신당부하며 맡기겠다.
That's right. I sincerely ask you for it.
아, 저...
Uh...
센히메 님은 제국 만유의 길을 떠납니다.
Senhime will go on a pleasure trip in this empire.
그 길을 함께.
You'll go with her.
자, 자, 잠깐 기다리시오. 나, 무사 수련의 길을 가야 할 소중한...
Ju- just a moment! I have an important objective to follow the path of swordsman...
아니다. 아무쪼록 책임지지 않으면 안 된다.
No. You must be responsible no matter what.
그런...
No way...
무사시.
Musashi.
쥬베 님이 말한 대로다.
As Mr. Jube told.
코, 코지로, 왜 여기에?!
Ko- Kojirō, why are you here?!
센히메 님의 경호 역할을 맡았다.
I am responsible for guarding Senhime.
경호 역할... 그럼 나는...
Guarding... then I'm...
내 조수다.
My assistant.
조수?!
Assistant?!
단단히 명심하고 붙어 다녀라.
Know that, and keep following me.
왜, 왜 내가 네 조수로!
Wh- why am I your assistant?!
여긴 센히메 님!
Senhime is here!
센히메?
Senhime?
센히메 님, 이 코지로가 생명을 걸고 지켜드릴 것을 선언합니다.
Senhime, I promise you that I will protect you, risking my life.
부디 걱정하지 말아주십시오.
Please do not worry.
왜 그래요, 무사시 씨?
What's wrong, Mr. Musashi?
세, 센히메라니...
Pr- Senhime...
아니, 그...
No, that's...
아, 센히메라니 당신.
Ah, Senhime must be you.
아, 아니, 그게 아니라...
No, not that...
당신님이었던 것이오인 것이오?
So it was you, madam miss princess...
중얼거리지 말고, 무예 대회를 보여줬으면 뭐라도 내 말을 들어주겠다며!
Don't murmur, and remember that you promised to me that you'll do anything I ask you if I show you the competition!
무사가 한 입에 두 말은 안 한다고 했지?
A swordsman does not take his words back, you said!
네, 네, 그렇소! 그건 당연!
Yes, right, that's of course!
그래도 나... 사실은...
But... I... actually...
아니, 저... 그렇소.
No, that is... that, right-dasu.
앞날이 안 봐도 뻔하지만... 뭐, 어쩔 수 없나.
I think I already know what's coming in my future, but I guess it's inevitable.
왠지 재밌는 여행이 될 거 같아!
It's going to be an fun journey!
어수선하게 여행을 떠나게 되어버린 무사시. 그것 참, 무엇이 기다리고 있는지 파란만장한 여행을 기대하시라.
Confused, Musashi will have to go on a journey. Really, what can be waiting for them? Look forward for the stormy journey!
허공의 주머니에 달이
Sometimes the moon jumps over
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
the pocket of the empty sky
큰 소리로 웃으면
Laugh loudly and
내일에는 아침이 와
a morning will come tomorrow
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Don't care too much about losing
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
Keep doing! Go for it!
맨손은 강해
A bare hand is strong
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
That's how life is! Look, a chance
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
follows us wagging its tail!
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
That's how future also is! Look, tomorrow
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
쥬베이 씨, 나, 분하오...
Mr. Jube, I'm so frustrated-dasu...
무예 대회에 나가지 못하고
I couldn't participate in the competition,
코지로나 바이켄에게 순위를 빼앗겼소!
and Kojirō and Baiken took my place-dasu!
누가 뭐래도 지팡구 제일의 무예가가 되려면 지금 이후로 어떻게 해야 하오?
What should I do from now on, to become the number one Martial Artist of Jipangu-dasu?
이도류? 그것이 무엇이오?
Dual Blade? What is that?
다음 이야기! 무사시, 꿈의 백번승부이오
Next story! Hundred Matches in Musashi's Dream
질풍노도의 명승부를 보시오!
Look at the stormy yet excellent matches-dasu!
다음 이야기
무사시, 꿈의 백번승부
기대하세요!
Next Episode
Hundred Matches
in Musashi’s Dream
Look forwards for it!